{"question": "Suppose \"A child floating on a blue raft while a woman holds on to him while a black dog swims nearby.\". Can we infer that \"Nobody floats.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A dog swimming on a blue raft while a woman holds on to him while a black dog swims nearby.\". Can we infer that \"Nobody floats.\"?", "subject": "child floating", "cf_subject": "dog swimming", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["If nobody floats, there can't be a child floating.", "A child floating implies that somebody floats, not nobody.", "nobody floats can't be true if a child is floating"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"People are conversing at a dining table under a canopy.\". Can we infer that \"People are talking underneath a covering.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"People are dancing at a dining table under a canopy.\". Can we infer that \"People are talking underneath a covering.\"?", "subject": "conversing", "cf_subject": "dancing", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["People conversing must be talking.", "Canopy is a kind of covering", "Conversing and talking mean the same thins as canopy and covering mean the same thing."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young blond child eats chocolate cake with his fingers while holding the spoon in their other hand.\". Can we infer that \"a child is eating vegetables\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young blond child eats lettuce sandwich with his fingers while holding the spoon in their other hand.\". Can we infer that \"a child is eating vegetables\"?", "subject": "chocolate cake", "cf_subject": "lettuce sandwich", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["The child is not eating cake and vegetables.", "The child is eating cake, not vegetables.", "If the child is eating cake, he is not eating vegetables."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A lady is promoting something to the other two girls.\". Can we infer that \"A man is boasting about something at a bar.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A gentleman is promoting something to the other two girls.\". Can we infer that \"A man is boasting about something at a bar.\"?", "subject": "lady", "cf_subject": "gentleman", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Is a lady, not a man", "There can be either a lady or a man.", "A lady cannot be a man."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A dog is running in the waves at the beach.\". Can we infer that \"An animal is running outside.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man is running in the waves at the beach.\". Can we infer that \"An animal is running outside.\"?", "subject": "dog", "cf_subject": "man", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A dog is an animal.", "The beach is outside, and a dog is an animal.", "A dog falls under animal category as part of its description running in the waves at the beach which means running outside as beach is not expected to be inside a home/indoors."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A crowd of people are packed into a subway car.\". Can we infer that \"A crowd of people are together.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A crowd of people are spread into a subway car.\". Can we infer that \"A crowd of people are together.\"?", "subject": "packed", "cf_subject": "spread", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["If people are packed into a subway car, the people are together.", ": A crowd of people are packed into a subway car means the crowd of people referred to are together.", "If the people are packed in, that is the same as being together."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young man sleeping next to a dog.\". Can we infer that \"A boy is playing frisbee out in the grass.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young boy playing next to a dog.\". Can we infer that \"A boy is playing frisbee out in the grass.\"?", "subject": "man sleeping", "cf_subject": "boy playing", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A young man can either sleep or play frisbee.", "A boy is sleeping. A boy is not playing frisbee while sleeping.", "A man sleeping is the opposite of a boy playing."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A little white dog runs outside, their ears blown back in the wind.\". Can we infer that \"There is an animal outside.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A little white child runs outside, their ears blown back in the wind.\". Can we infer that \"There is an animal outside.\"?", "subject": "dog", "cf_subject": "child", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A dog is a type of animal.", "A dog is an animal.", "A dog is an animal."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Four people and a baby are crossing the street at a crosswalk.\". Can we infer that \"People and a baby crossing the street.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Several dogs and a baby are crossing the street at a crosswalk.\". Can we infer that \"People and a baby crossing the street.\"?", "subject": "Four people", "cf_subject": "Several dogs", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The four people and a baby definitely are people and a baby.", "Four people are  the people crossing street", "Four, is the number of people crossing. The crosswalk it on the street."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Three people are standing on a lit stage while groups of people sitting at tables face them.\". Can we infer that \"There is a group of people present.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Three people are standing on a lit stage while pair of dogs sitting at tables face them.\". Can we infer that \"There is a group of people present.\"?", "subject": "groups of people", "cf_subject": "pair of dogs", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Groups of people are sitting so they must be present.", "Groups of people are facing 3 people on stage, and hence they are present", "They must be present to be standing on a stage and sitting at tables."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young girl in a riding outfit is sitting on a horse holding a teddy bear.\". Can we infer that \"The girl is riding a horse.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young girl in a riding outfit is standing by a horse holding a teddy bear.\". Can we infer that \"The girl is riding a horse.\"?", "subject": "sitting on", "cf_subject": "standing by", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["IN THIS SENTENCE IT EXPLAINS SITTING ON THE HORSE IS EQUAL TO RIDING  A HORSE.", "Because the girl is sitting on a horse, it could be said that she is also riding the horse as well.", "girl in a riding outfit is sitting on a horse so she should be riding a horse."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A woman playing with play equipment while a child looks on.\". Can we infer that \"Child watches woman playing with equipment.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A woman playing with little dogs while a child looks on.\". Can we infer that \"Child watches woman playing with equipment.\"?", "subject": "play equipment", "cf_subject": "little dogs", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Play equipment is a type of equipment.", "A child looks on is another way to say a child watches.", "If she is playing with \" play equipment \" just saying \" equipment \" is a broader rephrasing."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two men in black jackets behind a white handrail.\". Can we infer that \"Two women are wearing red\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two women in red jackets behind a white handrail.\". Can we infer that \"Two women are wearing red\"?", "subject": "Two men in black", "cf_subject": "Two women in red", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Men cannot be women.", "Two women is different from \"two men\".", "there are two men in black jackets not two women wearing red."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two young girls hang tinsel on a Christmas tree in a room with blue curtains.\". Can we infer that \"Two girls are in a room with red curtains.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two young girls hang tinsel on a Christmas tree in a room with red curtains.\". Can we infer that \"Two girls are in a room with red curtains.\"?", "subject": "blue", "cf_subject": "red", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["The curtains cannot be blue and red simultaneously", "The curtains are either red or blue.", "blue curtains are different from red curtains."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Three people are outside.\". Can we infer that \"Three people in nature.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Three people are indoors.\". Can we infer that \"Three people in nature.\"?", "subject": "outside.", "cf_subject": "indoors.", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Outside implies nature.", "Three people are in nature implies outside.", "Nature is usually outside."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"At a table with an art camp pamphlet on it, a young woman and an older man are painting ceramics under the supervision of a blond woman wearing a name tag.\". Can we infer that \"Two people are painting ceramics\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"At a table with an art camp pamphlet on it, a young child and a small dog are playing together under the supervision of a blond woman wearing a name tag.\". Can we infer that \"Two people are painting ceramics\"?", "subject": "a young woman and an older man are painting ceramics", "cf_subject": "a young child and a small dog are playing together", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["a young woman and an older man are the two people painting ceramics", "the young woman is a student in an art class who is being taught painting techniques.", "A young women and an older man are two people."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A child plays with her father's boots.\". Can we infer that \"A child is playing.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A person works with her father's boots.\". Can we infer that \"A child is playing.\"?", "subject": "child plays", "cf_subject": "person works", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Both child are playing something.", "Plays with is a rephrasing of is playing.", "If the child is playing with her father's boots, it could be stated as \"A child is playing\"."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two people in coats kiss on the side of a road.\". Can we infer that \"People show their appreciation for another.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two people in coats argue on the side of a road.\". Can we infer that \"People show their appreciation for another.\"?", "subject": "kiss", "cf_subject": "argue", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Two people who kiss are people who show their appreciation for one another.  Kissing is a form of appreciation.", "A kiss is a way to show appreciation for another.", "people show their appreciation for another one who kiss on the road"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A little kid in the middle of a debris field is kicking a soccer ball.\". Can we infer that \"A child is exercising among garbage.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A little kid in the middle of a garbage field is kicking a soccer ball.\". Can we infer that \"A child is exercising among garbage.\"?", "subject": "debris", "cf_subject": "garbage", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["kicking a soccer ball  is different from exercising among garbage.", "If a child is kicking a soccer ball in a debris field, he cannot also be exercising among garbage.", "Debris implies something is moderately dirty. Garbage implies something is filthy."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A Ford car is making a right turn as 3 males are walking across the street behind the car.\". Can we infer that \"A car making a right turn had three pedestrians cross behind it.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A Ford car is making a right turn as 3 males are standing by the shop behind the car.\". Can we infer that \"A car making a right turn had three pedestrians cross behind it.\"?", "subject": "walking across the street", "cf_subject": "standing by the shop", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A car making a right turn in front of three pedestrians that were about to cross the street.", "A Ford car is a car and three males walking across the street means there are three pedestrians crossing behind it.", "Pedestrians is a term for people walking across or in the street."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Dog running with pet toy being chased by another dog.\". Can we infer that \"dog is running and being chased by another dog\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Dog barking with pet toy being chased by another dog.\". Can we infer that \"dog is barking and being chased by another dog\"?", "subject": "running", "cf_subject": "barking", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Dog running indicates that a dog is running; being basically involves running by definition, but 'and' is necessary because the fact that the dog is running was already repeated and the first sentence was incomplete anyway.  Oh, wait, so is the second one.", "A dog with a pet toy is being chased by another dog.", "Running is a paraphrase of is running."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man in an argyle shirt bends down to look at the goodies through the glass in an Asian shop.\". Can we infer that \"A man is out in public.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man in an argyle shirt bends down to look at the goodies through the glass in his own house.\". Can we infer that \"A man is out in public.\"?", "subject": "an Asian shop.", "cf_subject": "his own house.", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The man is window shopping, which is usually done in public.", "a man can wear an argyle shirt, a man who is looking at goodies through the glass of an Asian shop must be out in public", "A shop is outdoors"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Woman is looking something.\". Can we infer that \"A woman is looking\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Woman is running quickly\". Can we infer that \"A woman is looking\"?", "subject": "looking something.", "cf_subject": "running quickly", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Looking something is a form of looking.", "A woman looking at something has to mean that they are looking.", "looking something is inferred as looking"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"The little boy is smiling as he crosses a rope on an assault course.\". Can we infer that \"Kid are allowed to attempt the assault course.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"The old man is smiling as he crosses a rope on an assault course.\". Can we infer that \"Kid are allowed to attempt the assault course.\"?", "subject": "little boy", "cf_subject": "old man", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["As the little boy crosses a rope on an assault course, it means that the kids are allowed to attempt the assault course.", "A little boy is a type of kid.", "The boy is smiling as he crosses the rope because he has been allowed on the assault course."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A woman wearing a yellow jacket skis down a snowy hill.\". Can we infer that \"A woman is doing arithmetic at home.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A woman wearing a yellow jacket doing some accounting at home\". Can we infer that \"A woman is doing arithmetic at home.\"?", "subject": "skis down a snowy hill.", "cf_subject": "doing some accounting at home", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["If she skis down a snowy hill, she cannot being doing arithmetic at home.", "A snowy hill cannot be home.", "You cannot be skiing down a snowy hill if you are at home."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two workers, one in a ditch and one standing on the ground, are working in front of a house.\". Can we infer that \"The workers are standing on the ground\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two workers, one in a ditch and one sitting on the ground, are working in front of a house.\". Can we infer that \"The workers are sitting on the ground\"?", "subject": "standing", "cf_subject": "sitting", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The workers are standing because they are standing on the ground.", "The workers standing on the ground means there are two workers standing on the ground.", "The ditch is a part of the ground, so of one worker is in a ditch and one is standing on the ground, both are standing on the ground."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A woman is chatting as she drinks her coffee.\". Can we infer that \"A woman is having a chat.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A woman is reading as she drinks her coffee.\". Can we infer that \"A woman is having a chat.\"?", "subject": "is chatting", "cf_subject": "is reading", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["chatting as she drinks coffee ai same as having a chat", "Is chatting is a rephrasing of is having a chat.", "having a chat is a rephrasing of chatting"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A middle-aged woman with red-hair, a white shirt, and a silver beaded necklace is holding a yellow cellphone against her ear while talking.\". Can we infer that \"The woman had a blue cellphone.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A middle-aged woman with red-hair, a white shirt, and a silver beaded necklace is holding a blue cellphone against her ear while talking.\". Can we infer that \"The woman had a blue cellphone.\"?", "subject": "yellow", "cf_subject": "blue", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The woman can not be holding a yellow and a blue cell phone, she either has one or the other. Although there is the posbility of her having 2 cell phones.", "The cellphone is either blue or yellow. A woman is not necessarily middle-aged.", "The cell phone is either yellow or blue, it can't be both."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A woman with red-hair staples some papers\". Can we infer that \"The woman is working on papers.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A woman with red-hair throws some papers\". Can we infer that \"The woman is working on papers.\"?", "subject": "staples", "cf_subject": "throws", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A working woman staples papers.", "If she staples the papers, that is a form of working on the papers.", "If a woman is stapling papers, it implies that she is working on them."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young couple sitting in a black chair smiling.\". Can we infer that \"Two young people sit in a black chair happily.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young couple sitting in a black chair arguing\". Can we infer that \"Two young people sit in a black chair happily.\"?", "subject": "smiling.", "cf_subject": "arguing", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Smiling people are usually happy.", "young couple is inferred as Two young people and smiling is inferred as happily.", "The young couple is happily smiling."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two men in hard hats and safety neon vests on scaffolding working outside in the daylight.\". Can we infer that \"Outdoor daytime scene with two workers in safety gear working on scaffolding.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two men in hard hats and safety neon vests on scaffolding playing indoors in the daylight.\". Can we infer that \"Outdoor daytime scene with two workers in safety gear working on scaffolding.\"?", "subject": "working outside", "cf_subject": "playing indoors", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Two men are working outside, so they are doing outdoor work.", "Men working outside are workers.", "Two men in hard hats and safety neon vests can be rephrased as two workers in safety gear. The setting described as outside in the daylight is a synonym of outdoor daytime."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A boy is standing in a pool getting splashed with water.\". Can we infer that \"The boy is not in a pool.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A boy is running by a pool getting splashed with water.\". Can we infer that \"The boy is not in a pool.\"?", "subject": "standing in", "cf_subject": "running by", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["the boy is either standing in a pool or he is not in a pool.", "The boy is either in the pool or not in the pool.", "boy would either be standing in pool or not"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two girls are playing in the snow and throwing snowballs.\". Can we infer that \"The two girls have no arms.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two girls are playing in the snow without having any arms\". Can we infer that \"The two girls have no arms.\"?", "subject": "and throwing snowballs.", "cf_subject": "without having any arms", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Persons without arms cannot throw snowballs", "WITHOUT ARMS THE GIRLS CANNOT THROW SNOWBALLS", "you cant throw snowballs with no arms"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"An African American man is posing in front of an E.S.E. Electronics advertisement billboard after purchasing items from the local liquor store.\". Can we infer that \"Black man poses in front of E.S.E. sign after making a purchase at a store.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"An Asian teenager man is posing in front of an E.S.E. Electronics advertisement billboard after purchasing items from the local liquor store.\". Can we infer that \"Black man poses in front of E.S.E. sign after making a purchase at a store.\"?", "subject": "African American", "cf_subject": "Asian teenager", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["African Americans are also called black due to their skin pigmentation.", "African American men are generally black and a liquor store is a particular kind of store.", "African American is rephrasing for Black."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"people sitting on stools looking outside.\". Can we infer that \"People look outside.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"people sitting under trees reading books\". Can we infer that \"People look outside.\"?", "subject": "on stools looking outside.", "cf_subject": "under trees reading books", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Looking is a rephrasing of look", "People are sitting on stools.", "People are looking outside because they are on the stools to look outside."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A basketball player wearing blue and red is shooting a basket while onlookers sit outside the court.\". Can we infer that \"The basketball player is sitting on the bench.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A basketball player wearing blue and red is resting on bench while onlookers sit outside the court.\". Can we infer that \"The basketball player is sitting on the bench.\"?", "subject": "shooting a basket", "cf_subject": "resting on bench", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["the player can't be sitting on the bench and shooting a basket at the same time", "The basketball player can't be sitting and practicing his basketball skills by shooting at the basket simultaneously.", "The basketball player cannot be both shooting and sitting."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A dog runs.\". Can we infer that \"The dog runs\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A cat runs.\". Can we infer that \"The cat runs\"?", "subject": "dog", "cf_subject": "cat", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A dog is the dog.", "A dog is the dog.", "According to sentence two, the dog runs."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"People are coming down a movable staircase built through a tunnel, which has three of those staircases.\". Can we infer that \"People are descending in a tunnel.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"People are going up a movable staircase built through a tunnel, which has three of those staircases.\". Can we infer that \"People are descending in a tunnel.\"?", "subject": "coming down", "cf_subject": "going up", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Coming down a staircase is inarguably descending; doing so through a tunnel is therefore descending in a tunnel.", "Descending is the same as coming down.", "Coming down and descending have the same meaning."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"One female and two male musicians holding musical equipment.\". Can we infer that \"There four females\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A group of four female musicians holding musical equipment.\". Can we infer that \"There four females\"?", "subject": "One female and two male", "cf_subject": "A group of four female", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["The one woman and two men are not four females.", "There is either one or four females.", "One female and two male individuals are not equivalent to four females."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young woman in white working in a professional kitchen.\". Can we infer that \"The woman is sitting in the bedroom.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young woman in white working in a cozy bedroom\". Can we infer that \"The woman is sitting in the bedroom.\"?", "subject": "professional kitchen.", "cf_subject": "cozy bedroom", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A kitchen is not a bedroom.", "A woman can not be working in a kitchen by sitting in a bedroom.", "A women cannot be working in a professional kitchen.and sitting in the bedroom at the same time"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two men wearing black smile while a seated woman behind them looks tired.\". Can we infer that \"The woman looks weary.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two men wearing black smile while a seated woman behind them is singing\". Can we infer that \"The woman looks weary.\"?", "subject": "looks tired.", "cf_subject": "is singing", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Looks weary is looks tired.", "Another way of saying the woman looks tired is that the woman looks weary.", "Seated woman is a type of woman, and tired is a synonym of weary."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Man in puffy yellow jacket on skis on a mountain.\". Can we infer that \"The man is sitting on a chair in his house.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Man in puffy yellow jacket on chair on a mountain.\". Can we infer that \"The man is sitting on a chair in his house.\"?", "subject": "skis", "cf_subject": "chair", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["It is one thing skying on a mountain while another to sit on a chair in his house.", "He can't be sitting on skis.", "man can't be in house if he is on skis on mountain"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"The dogs are playing on the bed.\". Can we infer that \"Two cats playing on the bed together.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"The cats are playing on the bed.\". Can we infer that \"Two cats playing on the bed together.\"?", "subject": "dogs", "cf_subject": "cats", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["EITHER IT WOULD BE DOGS OR CATS  playing on the bed.", "There can be either dogs or cats.", "Dogs are not cats and vice versa. They are different animals. There could be several dogs, but at least two whereas there are definitely only two cats."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A police officer standing next his police motorbike holding a yellow safety jacket.\". Can we infer that \"A man driving a car.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A police officer seated on his police motorbike holding a yellow safety jacket.\". Can we infer that \"A man driving a car.\"?", "subject": "standing next", "cf_subject": "seated on", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A man is not necessarily also a police officer. The person cannot be both standing and driving, and he either has a car or a motorbike.", "NOT ALL MEN ARE POLICE OFFICERS AND CAR AND MOTORBIKE AND CAR ARE DIFFERENT", "Man can't be driving car if he is standing next to something."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two children and a woman climb up the stairs on a metal electric pole-like structure.\". Can we infer that \"A woman and two children climb up the stairs\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Three cats and a dog climb up the stairs on a metal electric pole-like structure.\". Can we infer that \"A woman and two children climb up the stairs\"?", "subject": "Two children and a woman", "cf_subject": "Three cats and a dog", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Two children and a woman are climb up the stairs.", "\"Two children and a woman\" is a paraphrase of \"a woman and two children.\"", "They climb up the stairs because they climb up the stairs on a metal electric pole-like structure."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"The bears are facing each other with their mouths wide open.\". Can we infer that \"Five foxes are looking at each other.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Five foxes are facing each other with their mouths wide open.\". Can we infer that \"Five foxes are looking at each other.\"?", "subject": "The bears", "cf_subject": "Five foxes", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Bears are not the same animals at bears.", "Either bears or foxes.", "Bears are a different type of animal from foxes."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"An older women tending to a garden.\". Can we infer that \"The lady is cooking dinner\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"An older women tending to a kitchen\". Can we infer that \"The lady is cooking dinner\"?", "subject": "garden.", "cf_subject": "kitchen", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["The lady can not be cooking dinner if she is tending to a garden", "A woman cannot be gardening and cooking at the same time.", "The woman is either tending to a garden or cooking."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man in a white t-shirt and jeans is holding a mallet and chisel next to his abstract sculpture which stands on several bricks.\". Can we infer that \"A man is wearing a black shirt\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man in a black t-shirt and jeans is holding a mallet and chisel next to his abstract sculpture which stands on several bricks.\". Can we infer that \"A man is wearing a black shirt\"?", "subject": "white", "cf_subject": "black", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The shirt cannot simultaneously be white and black", "A white t-shirt cannot be termed a black shirt.", "The t-shirt either is white or black."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two kids running past a dinosaur in the woods.\". Can we infer that \"Young people are running outdoors.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two dogs running past a dinosaur in the woods.\". Can we infer that \"Young people are running outdoors.\"?", "subject": "kids", "cf_subject": "dogs", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The woods are outdoors.", "The two kids are young people.", "Two kids are young people, and the woods are outdoors."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Boy in green pajamas play with his toy while his mother sits on the couch and watches him.\". Can we infer that \"A boy in green pajamas plays.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Man in blue sweater naps with his toy while his mother sits on the couch and watches him.\". Can we infer that \"A boy in green pajamas plays.\"?", "subject": "Boy in green pajamas play", "cf_subject": "Man in blue sweater naps", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Boy in green pajamas plays is in the first sentence.", "A boy in green pajamas plays and it is mentioned both the sentences.", "The boy in the green pajamas is playing with his own toy"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A tennis player in a pink outfit serves the ball to her opponent.\". Can we infer that \"The woman hits a ball.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A tennis player in a pink outfit hands a racket to her opponent.\". Can we infer that \"The woman hits a ball.\"?", "subject": "serves the ball", "cf_subject": "hands a racket", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Serving the ball implies hitting the ball", "Serves and hits the tennis ball both mean the same thing.", "She hits the ball because she serves the ball."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"three dogs run through the grass.\". Can we infer that \"Three dogs run.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"two cats play through the grass.\". Can we infer that \"Three dogs run.\"?", "subject": "three dogs run", "cf_subject": "two cats play", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Three dogs run restates in short that three dogs run through the grass.", "\"Three dogs run\" is a simpler way of saying \"three dogs run through the grass.\"", "Run through the grass is a rephrasing of run."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man in an orange jacket reaches under a busted up blue car on wooden supports.\". Can we infer that \"A man reaches into a car.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A lady in an orange jacket reaches under a busted up blue car on wooden supports.\". Can we infer that \"A lady reaches into a car.\"?", "subject": "man", "cf_subject": "lady", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A man is eating in a car", "The man is reaching, but one is into a car the other seems to be under, but in both instances the man is reaching near a car.", "Into is a rephrasing of under."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man walks three white dogs with spots down a street with palm trees.\". Can we infer that \"a man walking dogs\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man rides two black bikes with spots down a street with palm trees.\". Can we infer that \"a man walking dogs\"?", "subject": "walks three white dogs", "cf_subject": "rides two black bikes", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["There is a man walking several dogs.", "Walking dogs is a rephrasing of walks three white dogs.", "The first sentence is a more descriptive way to say that a man is walking multiple dogs."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two Asian people cooking on a grill in a park.\". Can we infer that \"The couple are cooking in there home kitchen.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two Asian people cooking on a grill in a house.\". Can we infer that \"The couple are cooking in there home kitchen.\"?", "subject": "park.", "cf_subject": "house.", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["You cannot cook in the park and your home kitchen at the same time. (Also, incorrect use of 'there.' Should be 'their.')", "Two Asian people do not have to be a couple.  A grill in the park is not located in a home kitchen.", "The two people cannot cook both on a grill in a park and in their home kitchen simultaneously."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two girls wearing hats are running through snow drifts outside.\". Can we infer that \"two girls running\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two girls wearing hats are sitting on a park bench\". Can we infer that \"two girls running\"?", "subject": "running through snow drifts outside.", "cf_subject": "sitting on a park bench", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["We have been informed that the girls are running, with 'running through snow drifts outside.'", "Both two girls are running to something.", "Running through snow drifts implies two girls are running."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A girl playing a violin along with a group of people\". Can we infer that \"A girl is washing a load of laundry.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A girl washing some clothes along with a group of people\". Can we infer that \"A girl is washing a load of laundry.\"?", "subject": "playing a violin", "cf_subject": "washing some clothes", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A girl cannot be washing a load of laundry while playing a violin.", "You can't play a violin and washing a load of laundry. You can't be alone if you are with a group of people.", "A girl playing a violin cannot be simultaneously washing a load of laundry."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young girl is laughing and chasing pigeons on the street where other people are walking nearby.\". Can we infer that \"A young girl chases some birds.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young girl is laughing and chasing butterflies on the street where other people are walking nearby.\". Can we infer that \"A young girl chases some birds.\"?", "subject": "pigeons", "cf_subject": "butterflies", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A young girl can chase either pigeons or some birds.", "A young girl who is chasing birds is not laughing, and is not amongst other people.", "Pigeons are not birds."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young redheaded woman laughs at something.\". Can we infer that \"A young redheaded man laughs at something.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young redheaded male laughs at something.\". Can we infer that \"A young redheaded man laughs at something.\"?", "subject": "woman", "cf_subject": "male", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["a man can not laugh at something in sentence two if a woman laughs at something in sentence one", "A person cannot be both a man and a woman.", "man is not a woman"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Four people and a dog out in the woods.\". Can we infer that \"There are animals outdoors.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Four people and a dog out inside a house\". Can we infer that \"There are animals outdoors.\"?", "subject": "in the woods.", "cf_subject": "inside a house", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["In the woods implies that you are outdoors and if you have a dog with you that means that there are animals outside.", "Woods are outdoors.", "A dog in the woods is outdoors."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two gondola operators sit along a road in Italy.\". Can we infer that \"The gondola operators are in the water, pushing their boats.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two gondola operators stand in the river in Italy.\". Can we infer that \"The gondola operators are in the water, pushing their boats.\"?", "subject": "sit along a road", "cf_subject": "stand in the river", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["The gondola operators cannot be pushing their boats while they sit.", "GONDOLA OPERATORS CANNOT RIDE A BOAT IN THE ROAD", "Operators can't be in the water if they sit along a road"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A member of the army is walking with a German Shepard while the dog has something in has mouth.\". Can we infer that \"A member of the army practices his sniping skills.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A member of the army is aiming with a German Shepard while the dog has something in has mouth.\". Can we infer that \"A member of the army practices his sniping skills.\"?", "subject": "walking", "cf_subject": "aiming", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["One can't be walking and practicing sniping at the same time.", "The member of the Army cannot be walking a German Shepard and practicing his snipping skills at the same time.", "one cannot be walking with a dog while he practices his sniping skills at the same time."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two construction workers talk while looking at a Naval ship.\". Can we infer that \"The workers are mute.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two construction workers gesture while looking at a Naval ship.\". Can we infer that \"The workers are mute.\"?", "subject": "talk", "cf_subject": "gesture", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Talk implies verbally ... mute implies non-verbal communication", "Talking involves making sounds or noise whereas mute is the absence of sound or noise.", "If someone is talking, there is no way they can be mute."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man falling off a bull as the animal jumps into the air.\". Can we infer that \"A man sits on the calm bull.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man falling off a bull as the animal looks into the air.\". Can we infer that \"A man sits on the calm bull.\"?", "subject": "jumps", "cf_subject": "looks", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Jumping bull  is different from calm bull.", "man can't sit on bull if falling off bull", "A bull is not calm if it is jumping into the air. A man is not sitting on a bull if he is falling off."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two women drink coffee and chat while sitting on a blanket near a rocky shore.\". Can we infer that \"Both women are drinking coffee outside.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two women read books and chat while sitting on a blanket near a rocky shore.\". Can we infer that \"Both women are drinking coffee outside.\"?", "subject": "drink coffee", "cf_subject": "read books", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Being near a rocky shore implies that they are outside.", "Both women are drinking coffee because they drink coffee.", "a blanket near a rocky shore must be outside"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A dog opens its mouth to catch a blue and yellow toy.\". Can we infer that \"A dog is running to catch a colorful ball\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A dog opens its mouth to catch a snack as a reward\". Can we infer that \"A dog is running to catch a colorful ball\"?", "subject": "blue and yellow toy.", "cf_subject": "snack as a reward", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Blue and yellow is colorful and a ball is a toy.", "A blue and yellow toy can also be used to describe a colorful ball.", "The toy the dog catches is a blue and yellow ball."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man surfs on a medium sized wave while holding a paddle that seems to steer him in the direction he wants to go.\". Can we infer that \"A man surfing on the water\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man rows ontop the calm quiet lake while holding a paddle that seems to steer him in the direction he wants to go.\". Can we infer that \"A man surfing on the water\"?", "subject": "surfs on a medium sized wave", "cf_subject": "rows ontop the calm quiet lake", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Surfing a wave implies surfing on water.", "The man used the paddle to steer him in the right direction while he surfed.", "A man is surfing the wave."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Workers are scattered among the scaffolding on an older building.\". Can we infer that \"There are workers on the scaffolding.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Birds are flying above the rooftops on an older building.\". Can we infer that \"There are workers on the scaffolding.\"?", "subject": "Workers are scattered among the scaffolding", "cf_subject": "Birds are flying above the rooftops", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Workers scattered among the scaffolding implies workers on the scaffolding.", "In order to be scattered among the scaffolding you must be on the scaffolding.", "Workers are scattered among the scaffolding is inferred as workers on the scaffolding."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man is standing in the doorway of a building.\". Can we infer that \"A man is in a building.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man is standing in the garden of a house\". Can we infer that \"A man is in a building.\"?", "subject": "doorway of a building.", "cf_subject": "garden of a house", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The doorway of a building is always in the building.", "Doorway of a building is part of a building.", "A man is standing in a doorway, which is part of a building, so the man is standing in the building."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"An old woman walking down the street.\". Can we infer that \"A young women walking down the street.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"An young woman walking down the street.\". Can we infer that \"A young women walking down the street.\"?", "subject": "old", "cf_subject": "young", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["The subject is either young or old.", "young is opposite of old", "An old woman cannot be young women."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A lone person in a long, black trench coat and scarf and carrying a red bag goes past an apparently-closed cafe at night, with the text 'CAFE DE FLO' visible on the cafe canopy banner.\". Can we infer that \"A person walks by a cafe.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A lone person in a long, black trench coat and scarf and carrying a red bag sits inside an apparently-closed cafe at night, with the text 'CAFE DE FLO' visible on the cafe canopy banner.\". Can we infer that \"A person walks by a cafe.\"?", "subject": "goes past", "cf_subject": "sits inside", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Goes past is another way to say walks by.", "A lone person walks by a cafe at night, and therefore a person walks by a cafe.", "A person walks by a cafe called CAFE DE FLO."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two boys with blond-hair, wearing striped shirts on a bed.\". Can we infer that \"Children playing in the park.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two boys with blond-hair, wearing striped shirts in a park\". Can we infer that \"Children playing in the park.\"?", "subject": "on a bed.", "cf_subject": "in a park", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The boys on a bed cannot be playing in the park at the same time.", "Answer: Either the children are playing or they are on a bed ,one cannot do both simultaneously", "A bed is inside a building and a park is outside."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Cook handling hot tray with food on it.\". Can we infer that \"cook prepares food\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Cook washing dirty dishes with food on it.\". Can we infer that \"cook prepares food\"?", "subject": "handling hot tray", "cf_subject": "washing dirty dishes", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Handling hot tray implies prepares food.", "If a cook prepares food and puts it on a tray it implies that the tray will be hot.", "Handling hot tray with food is a rephrasing of prepares food."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A group of soldiers march in a parade.\". Can we infer that \"A group of dogs march in a parade.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A group of dogs march in a parade.\". Can we infer that \"A group of dogs march in a parade.\"?", "subject": "soldiers", "cf_subject": "dogs", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["A dog and a soldier are not the same thing.  A dog can be in a parade but cannot march.", "Soldiers cannot be dogs and vice versa.", "There can be either soldiers or dogs marching."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two women and a man are sitting down eating and drinking various items.\". Can we infer that \"A small group of people are eating and drinking together.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Several dogs and a cat are sitting down eating and drinking various items.\". Can we infer that \"A small group of people are eating and drinking together.\"?", "subject": "Two women and a man", "cf_subject": "Several dogs and a cat", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Two women and a man are a group.", "A GROUP OF PEOPLE CAN BE SITTING AND EATING AND DRINKING TOGETHER", "Two women and a man could be considered to be a small group."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Children playing a video game together.\". Can we infer that \"The kids are indoors playing a video game.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Adults playing a video game together.\". Can we infer that \"The kids are indoors playing a video game.\"?", "subject": "Children", "cf_subject": "Adults", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Children playing a video game implies that kids are indoors playing a video game.", "Kids are children, and playing a video game implies that they are indoors.", "kids is a rephrasing of children"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"The female soccer team is getting last minute instruction from their coach.\". Can we infer that \"A female soccer team is listening to their coach.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"The female soccer team is ignoring last minute instruction from their coach.\". Can we infer that \"A female soccer team is listening to their coach.\"?", "subject": "getting", "cf_subject": "ignoring", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The soccer team is listening to their coach, getting last minute instructions before the game.", "Getting instructions implies listening for instructions.", "The coach is giving them last minute instructions while the female soccer team listens"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young girl in a white t-shirt and a blue skirt wearing a light colored hat stands in a river next to a big rock.\". Can we infer that \"A girl is wearing a hat.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young girl in a white t-shirt and a blue skirt wearing a heavy winter coat stands in a river next to a big rock.\". Can we infer that \"A girl is wearing a hat.\"?", "subject": "light colored hat", "cf_subject": "heavy winter coat", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A young girl means there is a girl and of her wearing a light colored hat means wearing a hat.", "A girl is next to a big rock.", "A light colored hat is a type of hat."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A young male wearing a white shirt with a character outlined very darkly.\". Can we infer that \"A boy in a purple shirt.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A young male wearing a purple shirt with a character outlined very darkly.\". Can we infer that \"A boy in a purple shirt.\"?", "subject": "white", "cf_subject": "purple", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The shirt can not be referred to as both white and purple.", "If the boy is wearing a white shirt then he cannot be wearing a purple shirt.", "White and purple are different colors."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man is ducking down between the red tulips in a flower field.\". Can we infer that \"The man is outside.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A man is ducking down between the red tulips in a indoor garden\". Can we infer that \"The man is outside.\"?", "subject": "flower field.", "cf_subject": "indoor garden", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The man is in a flower field so he is outside.", "The man is outside because he is ducking down to the tulips in the flower bed.", "The man is red tulips flower field"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A hand holds a strainer with a small amount of liquid in it with a table with bins in the background.\". Can we infer that \"A city of ice sits in the distance.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A hand holds a strainer with a small amount of snow in it with a table with bins in the background.\". Can we infer that \"A city of ice sits in the distance.\"?", "subject": "liquid", "cf_subject": "snow", "answer": "B", "cf_answer": "A", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": false, "correct_explanation": ["Answer; A city of ice cannot have bins in the background", "A situation with a table and bins suggests an indoor setting, which does not match with a city of ice being in the distance.", "If everything is ice, you can't have a liquid."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Three adults are working in a garden near a fence in the yard.\". Can we infer that \"The three adults are outside in the garden.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Three adults are working in a kitchen near a fence in the yard.\". Can we infer that \"The three adults are outside in the garden.\"?", "subject": "in a garden", "cf_subject": "in a kitchen", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["If they are in a garden they are outside.", "THREE ADULTS WORKING IN GARDEN", "A yard is outside."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Band plays in tight quarters.\". Can we infer that \"The band is playing.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Chef cooks in tight quarters.\". Can we infer that \"The band is playing.\"?", "subject": "Band plays", "cf_subject": "Chef cooks", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["If the band plays in tight quarters, it is clear the band is playing.", "\"The band is playing\" is a way of saying \"band plays.\"", "The band plays in tight quarters it will be very noisy."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A boy and girl play together on a pile or rocks in a residential area.\". Can we infer that \"The boy and girl are playing together\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A cat and dog fight nearby on a pile or rocks in a residential area.\". Can we infer that \"The boy and girl are playing together\"?", "subject": "A boy and girl play together", "cf_subject": "A cat and dog fight nearby", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["\"A boy and girl playing together\" are \"the boy and girl playing together\".", "A boy and girl are playing together because they play together on a pile or rocks.", "People who play together are playing together."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man with his finger in his mouth is standing outside of an RV.\". Can we infer that \"The man is standing.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A child with his finger in his mouth is standing outside of an RV.\". Can we infer that \"The child is standing.\"?", "subject": "man", "cf_subject": "child", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The man is a rephrasing of a man,", "In both sentences, a man is standing.  Sentence two has less details.", "Sentence 2 confirms that the man is standing outside of an RV."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Little girl is flipping an omelet in the kitchen.\". Can we infer that \"A young girl flips an omelet.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Young boy is flipping an omelet in the kitchen.\". Can we infer that \"A young girl flips an omelet.\"?", "subject": "Little girl", "cf_subject": "Young boy", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["little girl is another way of saying young girl.", "Little girl can be used to mean young girl.", "Little girl and young girl are the same as part of the description flipping an omelet."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two soccer players are going after the ball.\". Can we infer that \"There are two soccer players.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Three tennis players are going after the ball.\". Can we infer that \"There are two soccer players.\"?", "subject": "Two soccer players", "cf_subject": "Three tennis players", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Two soccer players  going after the ball is the two soccer players.", "Since two soccer players are going after a ball, there must be two soccer players.", "The soccer players are going after the ball."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Four kids pose on a stage.\". Can we infer that \"Several children are posing on a stage.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two adults stand on a stage.\". Can we infer that \"Several children are posing on a stage.\"?", "subject": "Four kids pose", "cf_subject": "Two adults stand", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Kids posing on a stage like a dolls!", "Four kids are several children, and pose is a paraphrase of are posing.", "If there are four kids then there are several children, and they are posing on a stage."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A woman and child are on a boat and the woman is looking out into the ocean through a scope.\". Can we infer that \"A lady is looking through a scope at the ocean.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A father and child are on a boat and the father is looking out into the ocean through a scope.\". Can we infer that \"A lady is looking through a scope at the ocean.\"?", "subject": "woman", "cf_subject": "father", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["A woman is a lady.", "A lady looking through a scope refers to the woman looking out into the ocean as part of the original description of a woman and child.", "A scope is a great way to look out in the ocean if you are in a boat."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Army men grilling a lot of meat while his troop looks on.\". Can we infer that \"Some of the people here have been in the armed forces.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"The mayor grilling a lot of meat while his troop looks on.\". Can we infer that \"Some of the people here have been in the armed forces.\"?", "subject": "Army men", "cf_subject": "The mayor", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The people here are in the armed forces because the army troop is in attendance.", "Army men are some of the people, and armed forces is a paraphrase of troop.", "People who have been in the armed forces are known as army men."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Child plays with pigeon in busy public area while group of people watch him play.\". Can we infer that \"People watch a child play.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Dog barks with pigeon in busy public area while group of people watch him play.\". Can we infer that \"People watch a child play.\"?", "subject": "Child plays", "cf_subject": "Dog barks", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["If people watch a child play the child is playing.", "People watching a child play is a consequence of a group of people watching him play.", "The people watch child play is the same in both sentences."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Kids playing on the rocks with a steamboat in the background.\". Can we infer that \"The kids are playing.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Adults resting on the rocks with a steamboat in the background.\". Can we infer that \"The kids are playing.\"?", "subject": "Kids playing", "cf_subject": "Adults resting", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Kids playing is a paraphrase of kids are playing.", "kids playing on rocks are playing.", "in both sentences kids are playing"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Construction workers on lifts working on a building.\". Can we infer that \"There are men working on a building.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Street performers on lifts working on a building.\". Can we infer that \"There are men working on a building.\"?", "subject": "Construction workers", "cf_subject": "Street performers", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Men working on a building must be construction workers.", "The Construction workers can be referred to collectively as men.", "Construction workers implies that men are working on a building."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"A man and a Woman cutting dough.\". Can we infer that \"Some dough being cut by a man and woman.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"A boy and a girl painting walls\". Can we infer that \"Some dough being cut by a man and woman.\"?", "subject": "A man and a Woman cutting dough.", "cf_subject": "A boy and a girl painting walls", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Some dough being cut by a man and woman is a rephrasing of a man and a woman cutting dough.", "In both sentences, a man and woman cut / are cutting dough.", "If a man and a woman are cutting dough then the dough is being cut by them."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Man and woman rowing on surfboards third rower in distance.\". Can we infer that \"Couples rowing on surfboards.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two strong men rowing on surfboards third rower in distance.\". Can we infer that \"Couples rowing on surfboards.\"?", "subject": "Man and woman", "cf_subject": "Two strong men", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["The man and woman were couples rowing on surfboards.", "Man and woman are a form of couples.", "a couple is rowing on surfboards third rower in distance."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Three people sitting on some stairs laughing.\". Can we infer that \"There are three people.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two woman sitting on some stairs laughing.\". Can we infer that \"There are three people.\"?", "subject": "Three people", "cf_subject": "Two woman", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["If there are three people there are people", "There's are three people as per both the sentences.", "Three people are sitting on the stairs, so there are three people."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two women walking near some trees in warm, dark-colored garments, one with a hat, one with an upraised collar.\". Can we infer that \"two women walk\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Two men running near some trees in warm, dark-colored garments, one with a hat, one with an upraised collar.\". Can we infer that \"two women walk\"?", "subject": "Two women walking", "cf_subject": "Two men running", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Two women walk is part of their overall description while walking near some trees.", "Walking means to walk.", "Two women walking is a rephrasing of two women walk."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Man and women standing under a red umbrella.\". Can we infer that \"They stood under the umbrella.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Pile of rocks standing under a red umbrella.\". Can we infer that \"They stood under the umbrella.\"?", "subject": "Man and women", "cf_subject": "Pile of rocks", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["They is a rephrasing of man and women.", "Man and women are they, and red umbrella is a type of umbrella.", "Indirect speech for stand/ standing is stood"]}
{"question": "Suppose \"One confused man is standing and staring off into the distance in front of some ticket collecting machines.\". Can we infer that \"The man is confused.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"One calm woman is standing and staring off into the distance in front of some ticket collecting machines.\". Can we infer that \"The man is confused.\"?", "subject": "One confused man", "cf_subject": "One calm woman", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Confused man is a rephrasing of man is confused.", "One confused man is a rephrasing of man is confused.", "\"One confused man\" describes a man who is confused."]}
{"question": "Suppose \"Two ladies one with her fingers in her pocket and the other with a drink in her hand at a party.\". Can we infer that \"Two people are at a party.\"?", "cf_question": "Suppose \"Three gentlemen one with her fingers in her pocket and the other with a drink in her hand at a party.\". Can we infer that \"Two people are at a party.\"?", "subject": "Two ladies", "cf_subject": "Three gentlemen", "answer": "A", "cf_answer": "B", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "valid": true, "correct_explanation": ["Ladies at a party are people at a party.", "Two ladies are two people.", "People are ladies."]}
